KONRAD HAIGHT

(317) 506-5360 | konradhaight@gmail.com | LinkedIn

Summary

Professional with 10 years of experience in data management and analysis looking to translate that experience and new skills in software development into a career as a Salesforce Developer at a consulting firm.

Skills & Technologies

Skills:

- Data Analysis
- Data Management
- Project Management
- Data Quality Control
- Quantitative Analysis
- Research Design
- Program Evaluation
- Report Writing
- IRB Navigation
- Working Remotely

Technologies:

- C#/.NET Framework
- Salesforce
- HTML5/CSS/Bootstrap
- REDCap
- Microsoft Office
- SPSS

Professional Experience

Eleven Fifty Academy (Indianapolis, IN)

Learning Assistant

- · Aided students in understanding topics discussed in online modules and during class
- Helped students address syntax errors and debug broken code

American Institutes for Research (Indianapolis, IN)

Researcher

Expanded scope of 'Research Associate' position to include:

- Managed project IRB submissions, achieving approval on 100% of projects
- · Created project budgets and monitored spending on small budget projects with zero overruns
- Authored grant applications for 3 one-year secondary data analysis projects and won all three bids
- Created data governance plans

$\textbf{\textit{American Institutes for Research}} \ (Indianapolis, \ IN)$

Jul 2012 - Jul 2016

Research Associate

- Designed and implemented data analysis plans
- Designed and implemented data cleaning protocols
- Acted as liaison between project team and evaluation sites
- Managed data requests on secondary data analysis projects
- Managed grant application process, ensuring all grant requirements are met and individual pieces, maintained full coverage on projects
- Conducted interviews and focus groups with project participants

IUPUI Center for Criminal Justice Research (Indianapolis, IN)

Apr 2009 - Jul 2012

Research Assistant

- Led teams of students to collect data in the field resulting in a database of over 200,000 records that included every referral to the Indiana Juvenile Justice system over a 5 year period
- Processed and cleaned data that were collected by hand and those that were provided electronically

Education

Salesforce and Deloitte Pathfinder Program

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

Developer Certification (Certification exam passed on 9/3/2020)

- Salesforce and Deloitte joint program to build Salesforce Developer and business soft skills
- Completed 57 Badges and 1 Super Badge, achieved Trailhead Expeditioner rank
- Advanced technical skills include: Data management (incl. data modeling, security and data access), automation
 using workflow rules and process builder, reports / dashboards, writing custom components and applications using
 declarative tools and custom code

Eleven Fifty Academy Software Development Program

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

.NET Development

 Advanced technical skills include: C#, REST APIs, HTML5, CSS, ASP.NET, Entity Framework, Razor, MVC, Git/Github, Bootstrap

Jul 2016 - Present

Oct 2020 - Present

7-1-2012 7-1-201

For illustrative purposes only

Indiana University-Purdue University Indianapolis (Indianapolis, IN) *Bachelor's Degree in Criminal Justice*

Master's Degree in Criminal Justice and Public Safety

Aug 2005 - May 2015